Viewers all over the world,
to all hearts that are in bondage - bondage of unforgiveness, bondage of envy, jealousy -
be free, in the name of Jesus!
Open your lips - whatever hinders your deliverance,
right now, begin to give way, in the name of Jesus!
Whatever!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Holy Spirit, rain on us!
Your power of deliverance, rain on me!
Power! Glory!
Glory!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
I say to you, you disease -
Power! Out!
In your blood!
In your kidneys!
In your liver!
I say, "Out!"
In the name of Jesus!
Command it out!
Tell that disease, tell that sickness, say, "Out!"
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Come on!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Where can we go from His presence?
Rain, power of healing!
In the name of Jesus!
Prayer!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
TT: Mel Flowers 07/07/2018
RV ROBERT BEGIER 08/07/2018